A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 3, Series 15 FA1485
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants and Program Files, 1982-2012; 1
  - Stanford University - Monsen (20000390) - Correspondence (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Stanford University - Monsen (20000390) - Progress Reports (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Stanford University - Monsen (20000390) - Administration and Budget (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Stanford University - Monsen (20000390) - Project Development (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - American College of Physicians - Krause (20040690) (Box 125, Folder 5-6)
  - University of Arizona - Roubideaux (20030148) (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - University of Arizona - Roubideaux (20030148) - Grant Products (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - University of Arizona - Roubideaux (20030148) - Communication (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - University of Arizona - Roubideaux (20030148) - Meeting Materials, 2003 May 20-22 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - University of Arizona - Roubideaux (20030148) - Proposal Development, 2002-2003 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Grants Monitoring Program - Budget, Expenses and Budget Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Executive Nurse Fellowship, Program Review, Linda Aiken, University of Pennsylvania, 1996 December (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Identify Critical Activities-Evaluate Health Care Quality and Managed Care, Earl Steinberg, 1997 April (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Best Practices in Managed Care, K. Malroy, Mathematica Policy Research, Inc., 1997 May (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Grants Monitoring Program - July 1986 Board Write-Up and Background Information, 1986 July (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Grant Reviews (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Grants Monitoring Program - Strategy Meeting, Briefing Book, 1993 March 23 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Program Monitoring Committee Meeting, 1995 April 19 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Grantee Survey 1993, 1993-1994 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Grantee Survey 1993, 1993-1994 (Box 128, Folder 1-4)
  - Association of Maternal and Child Health Programs - Booth (20050221) - Improving Quality of Preventive Care in States, 2004-2005 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - MEM Associates (20010062) - Building Support for Healthy Steps, 2000-2002 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - MEM Associates (20000103) - Building Support for Healthy Steps, 1999-2001 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - MEM Associates (20020067) - Building Support for Healthy Steps, 2001-2003 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - University of Illinois - Niederman (20020427) - Evaluation of A Healthy Steps Residency Training Program, 2002-2005 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Economic and Social Research Institute (ESRI) (20010355) - Covering America - Issue Brief, 2002-2003 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Economic and Social Research Institute (ESRI) (20010355) - Covering America, 2001-2003 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - National Public Health and Hospital Institute (NPHHI) (990248) - Innovative Services for Children At-Risk, 1998-2000 (Box 130, Folder 3-4)
  - National Public Health and Hospital Institute (NPHHI) (990248) - Innovative Services for Children At-Risk, 1999 (Box 131, Folder 1-2)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy (20020047) - Stimulating New Developments in State Activity to Expand Access to Uninsured (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - University of Arkansas - Thompson (990433) - Quality Care for Children in Medicaid Managed Care, 1998-2002 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - University of Arkansas - Thompson (990433) - Quality Care for Children in Medicaid Managed Care - Grant Products, 2001-2003 (Box 131, Folder 5-6)
  - Georgetown University - Feder (990205) - Picker-Commonwealth Fund Long-Term Care for Frail Elders Program Direction and Policy Analysis, 1998-2003 (Box 132, Folder 1-4)
  - Georgetown University - Feder (990205) - Picker-Commonwealth Fund Long-Term Care for Frail Elders Program Direction and Policy Analysis - Grant Products (Box 133, Folder 1-2)
  - RAND Corporation - Morales (20020064) - Evaluating Ethnic Disparities in Patient Reports and Ratings, 2001-2005 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - RAND Corporation - Morales (20020064) - Evaluating Ethnic Disparities in Patient Reports and Ratings - Proposal Development, 2001-2003 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - RAND Corporation - Morales (20020064) - Evaluating Ethnic Disparities in Patient Reports and Ratings, 2001-2005 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - RAND Corporation - Morales (20020064) - Evaluating Ethnic Disparities in Patient Reports and Ratings - Grant Products, 2003-2005 (Box 134, Folder 1-2)
  - Center for Health Care Strategies - Somers (20020314) - Fact Sheets on Health Literacy, 2001-2003 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - New York University (NYU) - Berry (20020419) - Assuring Better Child Health and Development (ABCD): Support for Evaluation and Analysis, Phase Three, 2001-2004 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - New York University (NYU) - Berry (20020419) - Assuring Better Child Health and Development (ABCD): Support for Evaluation and Analysis, Phase Three - Administration, 2002-2004 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - New York University (NYU) - Berry (20020419) - Assuring Better Child Health and Development (ABCD): Support for Evaluation and Analysis, Phase Three - Proposal Development (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - New York University (NYU) - Berry (20020419) - Assuring Better Child Health and Development (ABCD): Support for Evaluation and Analysis, Phase Three - Grant Products (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - FACCT - Bethell (20010723) - Dissemination of Results from the Promoting Health Development Survey (PHDS) and Promoting Health Development Survey Plus (PHDS-Plus), 2001-2003 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Association of Maternal Health Program - Booth (20031406), 2002-2005 (Box 135, Folder 3-4)
  - National Opinion Research Center - Smith (20020690) - 2002 Survey of Trends in Employer Health Insurance, 2002-2005 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Penn State University - Short (20020516) - Filling Gaps in Health Insurance Over Time, 2002-2004 (Box 136, Folder 2-3)
  - Commonwealth Fund - Shur (20020197), 2002-2003 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Commonwealth Fund (20020197) - Proposal Development (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Commonwealth Fund (20020197) - Administration and Budget (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Gamble (20030304) - Minority Health Disparities: Bridging Research and Policy, 2003-2004 (Box 137, Folder 1-2)
  - Harvard - Edley (20030258) - Civil Rights Project, 2003-2005 (Box 137, Folder 3-5)
  - Harvard - Edley (20030258) - Civil Rights Project, 2002-2003 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - SUNY Downstate Medical Center - Andrulis (20040248) - Fourth Annual Conference - Quality Health Care, 2003-2005 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Summit Health Institute for Research and Education (SHIRE) - Congressional Briefing (20020347), 2001-2003 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Brandeis University - McDonaugh (20020504) - Reducing Racial and Ethnic Health Disparities: States as Catalysts for Change, 2002-2005 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Brandeis University - McDonaugh (20020504) - Reducing Racial and Ethnic Health Disparities: States as Catalysts for Change - Grant Products (Box 139, Folder 1-3)
  - Brandeis University - McDonaugh (20020504) - Reducing Racial and Ethnic Health Disparities: States as Catalysts for Change - Administration and Budget (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Brandeis University - McDonaugh (20020504) - Reducing Racial and Ethnic Health Disparities: States as Catalysts for Change - National Advisory Panel, 2002 October 31 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Brandeis University - McDonaugh (20020504) - Reducing Racial and Ethnic Health Disparities: States as Catalysts for Change - Correspondence (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Brandeis University - McDonaugh (20020504) - Reducing Racial and Ethnic Health Disparities: States as Catalysts for Change - Proposal Development (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - National Initiative for Children's Healthcare Quality (NICHQ) - Homer (20020386) - First Annual Forum for Improving Children's Health Care, 2001-2002 (Box 140, Folder 5-6)
  - National Initiative for Children's Healthcare Quality (NICHQ) - Homer (20030325) - Second Annual Forum for Improving Children's Health Care 2003 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - National Initiative for Children's Healthcare Quality (NICHQ) - Pearce (20040520) - Third Annual Forum for Improving Children's Health Care 2004 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Health Management Associates - Smith (20040684) - State Opportunities to Improve Healthcare Quality for Children, 2004-2005 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Institute for Health Care Improvement (IHI)-NICHQ - Homer (20010362), 2001-2002 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - NICHQ - Homer-Margolis (20010362) - Budget and Administration (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - NICHQ - Homer-Margolis (20010362) - Correspondence (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - NICHQ - Homer-Margolis (20010362) - Grant Products (Box 142, Folder 1-2)
  - AcademyHealth - Valentine (20030174) - AcademyHealth Research Meeting (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Northwestern University - Budetti (20010388) - Assuring Better Child Health and Development (ABCD) Project: Support for Evaluation and Analysis, Phase II (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Northwestern University - Budetti (20010388) - Assuring Better Child Health and Development (ABCD) Project: Support for Evaluation and Analysis, Phase II - Budget and Administration (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Northwestern University - Budetti (20010388) - Assuring Better Child Health and Development (ABCD) Project: Support for Evaluation and Analysis, Phase II - Proposal Development (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Northwestern University - Budetti (20010388) - Assuring Better Child Health and Development (ABCD) Project: Support for Evaluation and Analysis, Phase II - Grant Products (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Brandeis University - Yee (94-50), 1993-1995 (Box 166, Folder 1-3)
  - Brandeis University - Yee (93-78), 1993-1994 (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - Brandeis University - Yee (93-78), 1993 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Riley (990423) - Building State Medicaid Program's Capacity to Provide Child Health and Development Services - Proposal Development, 1999 (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Riley (990423) - Building State Medicaid Program's Capacity to Provide Child Health and Development Services - Administration and Budget, 1999 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Riley (990423) - Building State Medicaid Program's Capacity to Provide Child Health and Development Services - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Riley (990423) - Building State Medicaid Program's Capacity to Provide Child Health and Development Services - Articles and Background, 1999 (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Riley (990423) - Building State Medicaid Program's Capacity to Provide Child Health and Development Services - Grant Products, 1999 (Box 168, Folder 1-2)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - RFP Selection Committee, 1999 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Inquiries from States Re: RFP, 1999 (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - State Proposals in Response to RFP (990423), 1999 (Box 168, Folder 5-6)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Riley (20000419) - Building State Medicaid Program's Capacity to Provide Child Health and Development Services, Phase Two - Proposal Development, 1999-2000 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Riley (20000419) - Building State Medicaid Program's Capacity to Provide Child Health and Development Services, Phase Two - Articles and Background, 2000-2001 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Riley (20000419) - Building State Medicaid Program's Capacity to Provide Child Health and Development Services, Phase Two - Administration and Budget, 2000-2001 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Riley (20000419) - Building State Medicaid Program's Capacity to Provide Child Health and Development Services, Phase Two - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Riley (20000419) - Building State Medicaid Program's Capacity to Provide Child Health and Development Services, Phase Two - Grant Products, 2000-2001 (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Riley (20000419) - Building State Medicaid Program's Capacity to Provide Child Health and Development Services, Phase Two - Grant Products, 2000-2001 (Box 170, Folder 1-2)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Riley (20010387) - Building State Medicaid Program's Capacity to Provide Child Health and Development Services, Phase Three - Proposal Development, 2000-2001 (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Riley (20010387) - Building State Medicaid Program's Capacity to Provide Child Health and Development Services, Phase Three - Budget and Administration, 2000-2002 (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Riley (20010387) - Building State Medicaid Program's Capacity to Provide Child Health and Development Services, Phase Three - Correspondence, 2000-2002 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Riley (20010387) - Building State Medicaid Program's Capacity to Provide Child Health and Development Services, Phase Three - Grant Products, 2001-2002 (Box 171, Folder 2-4)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Riley (20010387) - Building State Medicaid Program's Capacity to Provide Child Health and Development Services, Phase Three - Grant Products, 2001-2002 (Box 172, Folder 1-2)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Riley (20020418) - Building State Medicaid Program's Capacity to Provide Child Health and Development Services, Phase Four - Proposal Development, 2001-2002 (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Riley (20020418) - Building State Medicaid Program's Capacity to Provide Child Health and Development Services, Phase Four - Budget and Administration, 2002-2003 (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Riley (20020418) - Building State Medicaid Program's Capacity to Provide Child Health and Development Services, Phase Four - Articles and Background (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Riley (20020418) - Building State Medicaid Program's Capacity to Provide Child Health and Development Services, Phase Four - Correspondence (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - National Academy for State Health Policy - Riley (20020418) - Building State Medicaid Program's Capacity to Provide Child Health and Development Services, Phase Four - Grant Products, 2002-2003 (Box 173, Folder 1-3)
  - ABCD Project State Initiatives (20020590), 2002-2003 (Box 174, Folder 1-2)
  - North Carolina - Yeager (20020593) - Proposal Development (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - North Carolina - Yeager (20020593) - Articles and Background, 2002-2003 (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - North Carolina - Yeager (20020593) - Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - North Carolina - Yeager (20020593) - Budget and Administration, 2002-2003 (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - North Carolina - Yeager (20020593) - Grant Products, 2002-2003 (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - North Carolina - Yeager (20020593) - Grant Products, 2002-2003 (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - Price Waterhouse Coopers - Rosenberg (990202) - Assessing a Small Business Health Insurance Demonstration in New York City - Proposal Development, 1998-1999 (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - Price Waterhouse Coopers - Rosenberg (990202) - Assessing a Small Business Health Insurance Demonstration in New York City - Administration and Budget, 1998-2000 (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - Price Waterhouse Coopers - Rosenberg (990202) - Assessing a Small Business Health Insurance Demonstration in New York City - Correspondence, 1997-2002 (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - Price Waterhouse Coopers - Rosenberg (990202) - Assessing a Small Business Health Insurance Demonstration in New York City - Articles and Background, 1999-2000 (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - Price Waterhouse Coopers - Rosenberg (990202) - Assessing a Small Business Health Insurance Demonstration in New York City - Grant Products, 1999-2002 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - United Hospital Fund - Tallon (96167) - Evaluation of Medicaid Managed Care in New York City, Phase One - Articles and Background (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - United Hospital Fund - Tallon (96167) - Evaluation of Medicaid Managed Care in New York City, Phase One - Correspondence (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - United Hospital Fund - Tallon (96167) - Evaluation of Medicaid Managed Care in New York City, Phase One - Administration and Budget (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - United Hospital Fund - Tallon (96167) - Evaluation of Medicaid Managed Care in New York City, Phase One - Grant Products (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - United Hospital Fund - Tallon (96167) - Evaluation of Medicaid Managed Care in New York City, Phase One - Grant Products (Box 177, Folder 1-2)
  - United Hospital Fund - Tallon (96167) - Evaluation of Medicaid Managed Care in New York City, Phase One - Proposal Development (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - United Hospital Fund - Gould (970265) - Evaluation of Medicaid Managed Care in New York City, Phase Two - Proposal Development (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - United Hospital Fund - Gould (970265) - Evaluation of Medicaid Managed Care in New York City, Phase Two - Administration and Budget (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - United Hospital Fund - Gould (970265) - Evaluation of Medicaid Managed Care in New York City, Phase Two - Currents (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - United Hospital Fund - Gould (970265) - Evaluation of Medicaid Managed Care in New York City, Phase Two - Grant Products (Box 178, Folder 3)
  - United Hospital Fund - Gould (970265) - Evaluation of Medicaid Managed Care in New York City, Phase Two - Proposal Development (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - United Hospital Fund - Gould (970265) - Evaluation of Medicaid Managed Care in New York City, Phase Two - Correspondence (Box 178, Folder 5)
  - United Hospital Fund - Gould (970265) - Evaluation of Medicaid Managed Care in New York City, Phase Two - Articles and Background (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Gray and Hadley (980182) - Impact of Nonprofit Hospital Conversion on Communities and Health System - Proposal Development, 1997-1998 (Box 178, Folder 7)
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Gray and Hadley (980182) - Impact of Nonprofit Hospital Conversion on Communities and Health System - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 178, Folder 8)
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Gray and Hadley (980182) - Impact of Nonprofit Hospital Conversion on Communities and Health System - Articles and Background (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Gray and Hadley (980182) - Impact of Nonprofit Hospital Conversion on Communities and Health System - Administration and Budget (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Gray and Hadley (980182) - Impact of Nonprofit Hospital Conversion on Communities and Health System - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Gray and Hadley (980182) - Impact of Nonprofit Hospital Conversion on Communities and Health System - Grant Products, 1997-2001 (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Gray and Hadley (980182) - Impact of Nonprofit Hospital Conversion on Communities and Health System - Grant Products, 2001 (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - George Washington University - Biles (20000224) - Impact of Medicare-Choice Program on the Elderly, Phase Two - Correspondence, 2000-2002 (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - George Washington University - Biles (20000224) - Impact of Medicare-Choice Program on the Elderly, Phase Two - Proposal Development, 2000-2002 (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - George Washington University - Biles (20000224) - Impact of Medicare-Choice Program on the Elderly, Phase Two - Articles and Background, 2000-2002 (Box 180, Folder 4)
  - George Washington University - Biles (20000224) - Impact of Medicare-Choice Program on the Elderly, Phase Two - Administration and Budget, 2000-2002 (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - George Washington University - Biles (20000224) - Impact of Medicare-Choice Program on the Elderly, Phase Two - Grant Products, 2000-2002 (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - George Washington University - Biles (20000224) - Impact of Medicare-Choice Program on the Elderly, Phase Two - Grant Products, 2000-2002 (Box 181, Folder 1-4)
  - Consumers Union - Bell (98044) - Proposal Development (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - Consumers Union - Bell (98044) - Administration and Budget (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - Consumers Union - Bell (98044) - Articles and Background (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - Consumers Union - Bell (98044) - Correspondence (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - Baruch College - Sofaer (990739) - Providing Medicare Beneficiaries with Report Cards to Compare HMO Quality in New York City - Administration and Budget, 1999-2001 (Box 182, Folder 5)
  - Baruch College - Sofaer (990739) - Providing Medicare Beneficiaries with Report Cards to Compare HMO Quality in New York City - Administration and Budget, 1999-2002 (Box 182, Folder 6)
  - Mathematica Policy Research - Gold (990481) - Proposal Development (Box 182, Folder 7)
  - Mathematica Policy Research - Gold (990481) - Articles and Background (Box 182, Folder 8)
  - Mathematica Policy Research - Gold (990481) - Administration and Budget (Box 182, Folder 9)
  - Baruch College - Sofaer (990739) - Providing Medicare Beneficiaries with Report Cards to Compare HMO Quality in New York City - Administration and Budget (Box 183, Folder 1-2)
  - Mathematica Policy Research - Gold (990481) - Correspondence (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - Mathematica Policy Research - Gold (990481) - Grant Products (Box 184, Folder 2-4)
  - University of Maryland - Stuart (990515) - Addressing the Cost of Prescription Drugs - Proposal Development, 1999 (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - University of Maryland - Stuart (990515) - Addressing the Cost of Prescription Drugs - Administration and Budget, 1999 (Box 185, Folder 2)
  - University of Maryland - Stuart (990515) - Addressing the Cost of Prescription Drugs - Articles and Background, 1999 (Box 185, Folder 3)
  - University of Maryland - Stuart (990515) - Addressing the Cost of Prescription Drugs - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 185, Folder 4)
  - University of Maryland - Stuart (990515) - Addressing the Cost of Prescription Drugs - Grant Products, 1999 (Box 185, Folder 5)
  - University of Maryland - Stuart (990515) - Addressing the Cost of Prescription Drugs - Grant Products, 1999 (Box 186, Folder 1-2)
  - Urban Institute - Moon (20000191) - Program Direction - Proposal Development (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - Urban Institute - Moon (20000191) - Program Direction - Articles and Background (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - Urban Institute - Moon (20000191) - Program Direction - Administration and Budget (Box 186, Folder 5)
  - Urban Institute - Moon (20000191) - Program Direction - Correspondence (Box 186, Folder 6)
  - Urban Institute - Moon (20000191) - Program Direction - Grant Products, 2000-2001 (Box 187, Folder 1-2)
  - Urban Institute - Moon (990204) - Program Direction - Proposal Development, 1999 (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - Urban Institute - Moon (990204) - Program Direction - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - Urban Institute - Moon (990204) - Program Direction - Administration and Budget, 1999-2001 (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - Urban Institute - Moon (990204) - Program Direction - Grant Products, 2000-2001 (Box 187, Folder 6)
  - Urban Institute - Moon (990204) - Program Direction - Grant Products, 1999-2000 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - Healthy Steps - ICF Incorporated - Proposal (20010115) (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - Healthy Steps - ICF Incorporated - Correspondence (20010115) (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - Healthy Steps - ICF Incorporated - Grant Products (20010115) (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - Healthy Steps - ICF Incorporated (20010234 and 2001007) (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - Healthy Steps - ICF Incorporated - Grant Products (20010115) (Box 204, Folder 5)